{
    "subject": "resource/Slovakia",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Euro_sign",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Slovakia is Euro.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8687871098518372,
            "question": "Is the Euro used in Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8158919215202332,
            "question": "What is the currency of Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7576776146888733,
            "question": "Are there any historical currencies used in Slovakia before adopting the Euro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5867648124694824,
            "question": "What are the benefits of using the Euro for Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5823231935501099,
            "question": "What is the history of currency usage in Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5427740812301636,
            "question": "What are the challenges of using the Euro for Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5353938937187195,
            "question": "How does the use of the Euro affect trade in Slovakia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49804985523223877,
            "question": "What other countries use the Euro as their currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4805038869380951,
            "question": "When did Slovakia adopt the Euro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3437056839466095,
            "question": "Is there any political debate surrounding the Euro in Slovakia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Slovakia is Euro.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8793_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Slovakia adopt the Euro?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8793_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other countries use the Euro as their currency?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8793_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the use of the Euro affect trade in Slovakia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8793_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8793_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. All five documents mention that the official currency in Slovakia is indeed the euro, with some providing additional details such as its abbreviation (EUR), subdivision into cents, and the fact that it replaced the Slovak koruna in 2008."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that the official currency of Slovakia is the euro, which supports the statement \"The currency of Slovakia is Euro.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}